Name=RevDiplomat
Author=Ostap_Blender
Conflict=
Dependence=
Priority=3
Section=Революция
SectionEng=Revolution
Languages=Rus,Eng
SmallDescription=Игровая ситуация про нападение на влиятельного дипломата
FullDescription=Группа пиратов нападает на влиятельного дипломата. Игрок может как защитить его, так и помочь пиратам.
FullDescription=Каждый из вариантов прохождения имеет свою награду.
SmallDescriptionEng=Game situation with pirate attack on influental diplomat
FullDescriptionEng=A group of pirates attacks an influental ambassador. Player may either shield him, or help the pirates.
FullDescriptionEng=Every variant of situation's ending have it's own reward.