Name=RefSaveDeposit
Author=Marshalska Rokossovsky
Conflict=
Dependence=UtilityFunctionsPack
Priority=2
Section=Reflection
SectionEng=Reflection
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Депозит и кредит больше не исчезают
FullDescription=При уничтожении бизнес-центров кредит и депозит не пропадают насовсем, а ожидают постройки бизнес-центра
FullDescription=В качестве "извинения за неудобства" за кредит не начисляются проценты, а за депозит - наоборот, начисляются

SmallDescriptionEng=Reaction to the use of the transfactor beacon and subportal
FullDescriptionEng=Now your machinations will not go unnoticed by the defenders of the system - their radars can pick up the frequencies of the transfactor beacon, and then all the anger of the Coalition/ Clan will fall on you!
