Name=ShuMM
Author=Mr Shu, SINIGR, Рейнджер Волк, Klaxons, LEOPARD, Ostap_Blender, Elemental Games
Conflict=
Dependence=
Priority=5
Section=Shu's Rangers
Languages=Rus,Eng
SmallDescription=Новые микромодули и акрины
FullDescription= Добавляет в игру более десятка новых микромодулей, в том числе выпадающих только с пиратов / доминаторов
FullDescription=- Добавляет новое планетарные акрины, уникальные для каждой из рас, в том числе для пиратов
FullDescription=- Добавляет возможность отыскать на необитаемой планете корпус "Таухито"
FullDescription=- Добавляет уникальное акриновое оборудование: генератор энергии, энергенный и импульсный двигатели
FullDescription=- Добавляет акриновую модификацию для ракетомета "Торпедо"
SmallDescription=New micromodules and acrynes
FullDescription= Adds into the game more than ten new micromodules, including ones that drops only from dominators / pirates.
FullDescription=- Adds new planetary acrynes, unique for each race, pirates included: Armorite, Biogenetic droids, Bipolar radar, Cybernetic gripper, ScanBot scanner, pirate acryne equipment series and coalition's microgenic series.
FullDescription=- Adds an possibility of finding hull Tauhito on uninhabitable planet
FullDescription=- Adds unique acryne equipment: energy generators, energenic engines, unique for each race hulls
FullDescription=- Adds new acryne modification for missile launcher - Torpedo