Name=Assistant
Author=Huk, Обер
Conflict=
Dependence=
Priority=4
Section=Прочие моды
SectionEng=Other Mods
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Добавляет удобный игровой "ассистент" <color=0,132,15>(легален)</color>
SmallDescription=(Мод можно <color=0,150,15>подключать</color>/<color=150,0,15>отключать</color> в течение партии)
FullDescription=Мод добавляет в игру ряд удобных кнопок, значительно облегчающих жизнь, но в то же время никак не влияющих на баланс.
FullDescription=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescription=<color=0,50,200>Новые кнопки:</color>
FullDescription=- Позволяет просматривать на ЦР цепочку готовящихся к выдаче микромодулей, а в космосе - альтернативную цепочку по конкретному ЦР
FullDescription=- В меню корабля (трюм) добавлены две кнопки, позволяющие просматривать статистику игрока и вызывать всплывающие окна со всем установленным оборудованием, при этом кнопка показа оборудования работает в меню просмотра всех кораблей, которые игрок может просканировать
FullDescription=- Добавлена кнопка быстрой перемотки времени, доступная игроку на всех планетах и базах
FullDescription=- Добавлена кнопка поиска корабля по имени, доступная игроку в космосе
FullDescription=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescription=-Мод доковырян VarWiZZ до рабочего состояния в 2448, добавлено суммирование бонусов на виде скриншота, уменьшено количество ММ в списках цепочек с 51 до 48 для разрешения 720, весь текст выведен из Main.dat в Lang.dat и добавлена английская локализация.
FullDescription=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescription=<color=0,132,15>Мод легален.</color>
FullDescription=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescription=-Changes by VargWiZZ: fixed compatbility with 2448+, added acryn bonus sum on the photo button, decreased mm amount in the chain list from 51 to 48 to accomodate for 720 height screen resolution, all text moved from Main.dat to Lang dat so English localization could be presented properly.
FullDescription=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescription=<color=0,132,15>Mod  is legal.</color>

SmallDescriptionEng=<color=250,20,20>Warning! Untranslated staff!</color> Add a handy game "assistant" <color=0,132,15>(legal)</color>
FullDescriptionEng=The mod adds a number of convenient buttons to the game, making life much easier, but at the same time does not affect the balance.
FullDescriptionEng=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescriptionEng=<color=0,50,200>New buttons:</color>
FullDescriptionEng=- Allows you to view a chain of micromodules about to be issued on a RC, and in space, an alternate chain for a particular RC
FullDescriptionEng=- Two buttons have been added to the ship menu (hold) that allow you to view the player's stats and bring up pop-up windows with all installed equipment, with the equipment show button working in the view menu of all ships the player can scan
FullDescriptionEng=- Added a fast forward time button available to the player on all planets and bases
FullDescriptionEng=- Added a ship search button by name available to the player in space
FullDescriptionEng=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescriptionEng=-The mod has been tweaked by VarWiZZ to a working state of 2448, a summation of bonuses has been added in the form of a screenshot, the number of MMs in the lists of chains has been reduced from 51 to 48 for a resolution of 720, all text has been moved from Main.dat to Lang.dat and English localization has been added.
FullDescriptionEng=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescriptionEng=<color=0,132,15>The mod is legal.</color>
FullDescriptionEng=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescriptionEng=-Changes by VargWiZZ: fixed compatbility with 2448+, added acryn bonus sum on the photo button, decreased mm amount in the chain list from 51 to 48 to accomodate for 720 height screen resolution, all text moved from Main.dat to Lang dat so English localization could be presented properly.
FullDescriptionEng=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescriptionEng=<color=0,132,15>Mod  is legal.</color>
