Name=EvoFreeInflation
Author=Klaxons
Dependence=EvoFairTrade, UtilityFunctionsPack
Conflict=EvoNoInflation
Priority=2
Section=Эволюция
SectionEng=Evolution
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Отвязывает галактическую инфляцию от среднего капитала активных рейнджеров
FullDescription=Данный мод позволяет отвязать галактическую инфляцию от среднего капитала рейнджеров, включая капитал игрока.
FullDescription=<br>
FullDescription=<color=0,50,200>Это окажет непосредственное влияние на:</color>
FullDescription=- Награды за задания
FullDescription=- Стоимость ошмётков и прочих квестовых предметов
FullDescription=- Цены различных услуг и улучшений
FullDescription=- Незначительные изменения цены товаров (хотя от среднего капитала они не зависят), а также расширение период их инфляционного роста с 3326 до 4000 года (однако, к общей инфляции они, по-прежнему, не привязаны)
FullDescription=<br>
FullDescription=Цены на оборудование в магазинах затронуты не будут, т.к. они никогда не были привязаны к общей инфляции и зависят исключительно от ТУ и качества самого предмета.
FullDescription=<br>
FullDescription=<color=255,0,0>Рекомендуется подключать до начала новой партии игры.</color>

SmallDescriptionEng=Detaching galactic inflation from the average capital of active rangers
FullDescriptionEng=This mod allows you to detach galactic inflation from the average rangers capital, including the player's capital.
FullDescriptionEng=<br>
FullDescriptionEng=<color=0,50,200>This will have a direct impact on:</color>
FullDescriptionEng=- Quest rewards
FullDescriptionEng=- Costs of scraps and other quest items
FullDescriptionEng=- Prices for various services and improvements
FullDescriptionEng=- Minor changes in the price of goods (although they do not depend on the average capital), and so their expansion period of inflationary growth will be increased from 3326 to 4000 years (however, they are still not tied to general inflation)
FullDescriptionEng=<br>
FullDescriptionEng=Prices of equipment will not be affected as they have never been tied to main inflation and depends solely of the technical specifications and the quality of the equipment itself.
FullDescriptionEng=<br>
FullDescriptionEng=<color=255,0,0>It is adwisely recommended to enable this mod before starting a new game.</color>