Name=RefPBFree
Author=Marshalska Rokossovsky
Dependence=PBEngine
Priority=80
Section=Reflection
SectionEng=Reflection
Languages=Rus,Eng

SmallDescription=Делает постройку всего бесплатным в ПБ (для теста и веселья)
SmallDescription=<color=255,128,0>ПЕРИОДИЧЕСКИ ТРЕБУЕТСЯ ПЕРЕПОДКЛЮЧИТЬ</color>
FullDescription=Делает постройку всего бесплатным в ПБ (для теста и веселья) ПЕРИОДИЧЕСКИ ТРЕБУЕТСЯ ПЕРЕПОДКЛЮЧИТЬ В СЛУЧАЕ НЕРАБОТЫ

SmallDescriptionEng=Large-scale rebalancing of planetary battles<color=255,128,0> (makes gameplay more difficult)</color>
FullDescriptionEng=The main concept of the mod:<color=255,128,0> adaptability and variability</color> .
FullDescriptionEng=Adds the need to maintain<color=255,128,0> resource management</color> and creating assemblies for specific situations.
FullDescriptionEng=All completely redesigned<color=255,128,0> robot templates for AI</color> : new ones have been added, ineffective ones have been removed.
FullDescriptionEng=The robots from the reinforcements have been reinforced.
FullDescriptionEng=The cost of all components and turrets has been revised.
FullDescriptionEng=The machine gun turret has been replaced with a discharge turret (disables robots).
FullDescriptionEng=The characteristics of all turrets have been changed: each has strengths and weaknesses.
FullDescriptionEng=Changed the stats of all guns: some deal more damage to turrets, others to robots.
FullDescriptionEng=Robot heads have been redesigned: each of them specifies the robot's specialization.
FullDescriptionEng=The characteristics of bodies have been reworked: early ones have more HP and vice versa.
FullDescriptionEng=Each undercarriage now has its own bonuses for ascending, descending, and moving on the water.
FullDescriptionEng=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescriptionEng=In my variation of the mod, the HP of torsos has been revised: an extremely strong skew in HP causes extremely strange situations when a battalion of super-strong robots with a huge DPS is ruined by a bunch of cheap, but VERY fat robots.
