Name=ExpArts
Author=Huk, Klaxons, LEOPARD
Conflict=
Priority=1
Dependence=UtilityFunctionsPack
Section=Экспансия
SectionEng=Expansion
Languages=Rus,Eng
SmallDescription=Добавляет в игру новые предметы и артефакты
SmallDescriptionEng=Adds new items and artifacts to the game.
FullDescription=<color=0,50,200>Новые предметы и артефакты:</color>
FullDescription=- Техдиструптор (артефакт) - осколочное оружие игнорирует ГЗП и броню корпуса цели с шансом в 25%
FullDescription=- Рефлектор (артефакт) - обнуляет урон от звезды, при этом быстро изнашиваясь, а если на расстоянии 330 ед. от корабля есть противники, то отражённый урон перенаправляется в них
FullDescription=- Бустер (артефакт) - увеличивает точность наведения и скорость полёта ракет, но при этом максимальная продолжительность их полёта снижается
FullDescription=- Хаскер_PROx64 (артефакт) - подключается к каналу коммуникатора и крадёт кредиты у корабля, с которого вы успешно потребовали выкуп, либо выкидывает дополнительный груз при его успешном истребовании
FullDescription=- Нуль-генератор (одноразовый предмет) - позволяет совершить прыжок в другую систему из любой части карты
FullDescription=- Контейнер с бомбами пиратского клана - содержит в себе различные бомбы и детонаторы
FullDescription=- Оглушающая бомба - корабли в радиусе 250 ед. теряют контроль и некоторое время крутятся на месте, полностью теряя возможность вести огонь (не действует на боссов и базы)
FullDescription=- ЭМП бомба - наносит серьёзные повреждения всему оборудованию кораблей в радиусе 250 ед.
FullDescription=- Детонатор для бомбы - крепится к бомбе и вызывает детонацию при контакте корабля или через заданное число ходов
FullDescription=- Контейнер с кустарной модификацией пиратского клана - содержит в себе одну случайную модификацию для оборудования (всего 11 различных модификаций)
FullDescription=- Декалератор (улучшение) - накладывает на энергетическое оружие способность замедления цели
FullDescription=- Асидий (улучшение) - накладывает на осколочное оружие способность ослаблять броню цели
FullDescription=- Отсек контрабандиста (улучшение) - расширяет трюм корабля, но также повышает его восприимчивость к урону
FullDescription=<clr><clrEnd>
FullDescription=Все новые предметы и артефакты закапываются на незаселённых планетах в начале игровой партии.
FullDescription=Также некоторые пираты теперь при смерти выбрасывают случайную бомбу с взведённым таймером (подбирать не рекомендуется).
FullDescriptionEng=<color=0,50,200>Adds new items and artifacts:</color>
FullDescriptionEng=- Techdistruptor (artifact) - Fragmentation weapons have a 25% chance to ignore shield field and hull armor
FullDescriptionEng=- Reflector (artifact) - Nullifies damage from stars, while wearing out quickly. If there are enemies at a distance of up to 330, the damage is reflected to them
FullDescriptionEng=- Booster (artifact) - Improves missile tracking systems and flight speed of rocket weapons, while also reducing the maximum duration of missile flight
FullDescriptionEng=- Hasker_PROx64 (artifact) - Connects to the receiver via the communicator. Pilots you demand money from will lose a bit more than they planned. When dropping cargo, the ship's cargo systems discard more than supposed to
FullDescriptionEng=- Null-generator (disposable artefact) - Allows you to jump to any system from any part of the map
FullDescriptionEng=- Bomb container - Contains various bombs and detonators. Most likely belongs to the Pirate Clan
FullDescriptionEng=- Stun bomb - Ships within a radius of 250 units lose control and spin in place for a while, completely losing the ability to fire. (does not affect bosses and bases)
FullDescriptionEng=- EMF bomb - Deals serious damage to all devices and equipment of ships within a radious of 250
FullDescriptionEng=- Detonator - Attached to the bomb, causes detonation upon contact with any ship, or after a specified amount of time
FullDescriptionEng=- Container with modification kits, сontains 1 random modification (out of 13 available)
FullDescriptionEng=- Decelerator (improvement) - Imposes the ability to slow down the target by energy weapons
FullDescriptionEng=- Till capacitors (improvement) - Increases energy weapon's damage at the expense of reliability
FullDescriptionEng=- Acidius (improvement) - Acidifies fragmentation weapons ammo, lowering the target's armor
FullDescriptionEng=- Twisted limiters (improvement) - Increases firing range of fragmentation weapons at the expense of reliability
FullDescriptionEng=- Additional stowage (improvement) - Increases missile capacity
FullDescriptionEng=- Processors "Extreme" (improvement) - Boosts droid repair potential
FullDescriptionEng=- Security systems replacement (improvement) - Removes security system from fuel tank to increase it's capacity
FullDescriptionEng=- Hacked injector (improvement) - Increases engine speed by allowing more fuel into the engine
FullDescriptionEng=- Reinforced servo drives (improvement) - Enhances gripper allowing it to move heavier loads
FullDescriptionEng=- Field density amplifier (improvement) - Increases strength of protective bubble from shield generator at the expense of reliability
FullDescriptionEng=- Meon chips (improvement) - Increases radar range at the expense of reliability
FullDescriptionEng=- Circuit amplifier (improvement) - Increases scanner power at the expense of reliability
FullDescriptionEng=- Fragilium parts (improvement) - Increases equipment reliability
FullDescriptionEng=- Smuggler's compartment - Expands the cargo hold of the ship, but also increases the ship's susceptibility to damage
FullDescriptionEng=<br>
FullDescriptionEng=All new items and artifacts are buried on unpopulated planets at the beginning of the game.
FullDescriptionEng=Additionally, some pirates will now drop a random bomb with a set timer when they die (it is not recommended to pick them up).